# Jen Frazier

Chicago, IL (901) 246-1750 jen.frazier1@gmail.com

# **UX Designer**

<u>Github</u> LinkedIn

After being in occupational therapy for 13 years I became mesmerized by the similarities and fresh perspective offered in UX design. Creativity, problem-solving, task segmentation, user flows, and interviews are things I have been doing daily in healthcare and I am so excited to be able to incorporate them in a new and clever way. Being a designer allows me to help people through communicating a story and evoking emotions while utilizing my weird creative stylings.

### **Skills**

**Approaches:** UX design, UI design, User research, Competitive analysis, User stories, User personas, User testing, Visual design, Branding, Prototyping, Mockups

Tools and Languages: Figma, Sketch, InVision Studio, GitHub, Git, HTML5, CSS

# **Projects**

#### Caspian | InVision: https://invis.io/TCWERIYBUJP

- Created a cloud storage app designed to add organization and community to the users experience
- Implemented UX/UI approaches while solving the problems noted in research to incorporate a dramatic story to the branding and design.

# **Education**

Thinkful Remote

#### **Bloc Design Program**

- Learned industry best practices and design process standards with a focus on UX research, Visual design, and frontend development.
- Created and deployed projects while learning new tools and frameworks by collaborating several hours every week with a senior product designer.

Second City Chicago, IL

#### **Professional Conservatory Program**

2014

• Professional certificate of completion for competitive improvisation and sketch comedy program.

#### Nashville State Community College Associate Degree of Applied Science: Occupational Therapy Assistant

Nashville, TN

2006

# **Experience**

### Select Rehabilitation, REX Therapeutics, QTC

Chicago, IL

#### **Certified Occupational Therapy Assistant**

2002 - September 2019

- Increase problem-solving success for patients to reach their highest level of independence.
- Execute task segmentation for increased ease with patient's self-care tasks.
- Educate staff on best practices and safety with patient care.
- Mentor OT students to educate, encourage, and support newcomers to the field.

# Improvisation and Sketch Comedy Performer

Chicago, IL

2012 - 2016

- Utilized my compassionate, outgoing personality to connect with audiences weekly
- Partnering with fellow comedians, I created a safe space for guests to laugh and have fun

# Rehabilitation Department Director

Second City

RehabCare

Memphis, TN 2009- 2010

Managed interdisciplinary team through weekly staff assessments and documentation training

• Delivered monthly presentation to the senior citizen community with knowledge to identify/address health challenges